Zahra Ganji

Contact Information Dept. Computer Engineering (CE) Amirkabir University of Technology (AUT) No.424 Hafez Ave., Tehran, Iran

Email: zra.ganji@gmail.com Email (academic): zganji@aut.ac.ir GitHub: Github.com/ZahraGanji Homepage: s-ganji.github.io Cell Phone:(+98) 919 077 8117

Research Interest Machine Learning Data Mining

• Computer Networks

Natural Language Processing

EDUCATION

 Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic), Tehran, Iran (Ranked 2nd among all Iranian engineering universities)

B.Sc., Computer Engineering, Sep 2016 - Apr 2021

- GPA: 15.65/20 - 140/140 credits

- GPA over the last important 60 credits: 18.09/20

· Farzanegan High School, Tehran, Iran

(National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (NODET))

Diploma in Mathematics and Physics, Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

- GPA: High School 19.55/20, Pre-University 19.51/20

Relevant Coursework • Data Mining: 20/20

• Web Programming: 20/20

• Principles of Database Design: 17.6/20

• Database Design Lab.: 20/20

• Principles of Computational Intelligence: 16/20

• Algorithm Design: 15.5/20

Introduction to Bioinformatics: PASS*

• Information Retrieval: PASS*

* COVID-19 Semester(Grades were binary due to COVID-19)

• Principles of Management: 20/20

• Information Technology Project Management: 18/20

• Multimedia Systems: 18.5/20

• Information Security: 18.7/20

• Engineering Statistics: 17.1/20

• Computer Networks: 15.9/20

• Startup Development: PASS*

Internet of Things: PASS*

Online Courses

- · Mathematics for Machine Learning: Linear Algebra
- IBM Data Science Specialization

Publications

• Ganji, Z., Shokri, S. and Ganji, H. (2022). Prediction of gas hydrate formation condition by data-driven modeling: Different machine learning models with vector quantization and cuckoo search algorithm. Submitted to Journal of Computers and Industrial Engineering (CAIE).

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic), Tehran, Iran

- Instructor, C programming Language Lab. Under supervision of Prof. Bahador Bakhshi and Prof. Hossein Zeinali (Fall 2020-2021)
- Teaching Assistant, Computational Intelligence Instructor: Prof. Mohammad Mahdi Ebadzadeh (Fall 2020-2021)
- Teaching Assistant, Logic Circuits Instructors: Prof. Mehdi Sedighi and Prof. Morteza Saheb Zamani (Fall 2020-2021)
- Teaching Assistant, Electric Circuits Instructors: Prof. Mahmoud Momtazpour (Fall 2019-2020)

Work Experience

- Hami System Sharif, Tehran, Iran (Jun 2019 Sep 2019)
 Web Development Intern. (Linux (Ubuntu), Laravel, HTML, PHP, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL)
- Papion, Tehran, Iran (Jun 2017- Sep 2017)
 Web Development Intern. (HTML, PHP, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL)

Honors & Awards

- Achieved top 1% place among all applicants of the **Nationwide University Entrance Exam** for B.Sc. in Engineering (Approximately 163000 applicants), Iran, 2016.
- Accepted in NODET High School Entrance Exam, National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents, Iran, 2012

EXTRACUR-RICULAR EXPERIENCE

 Staff member and member of executive committee of the 17th & 18th ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) and Linux Festival at Computer Engineering and IT Department, Amirkabir University of Technology, 2017 - 2018 NOTABLE ACADEMIC COURSE PROJECTS

Deep Convolutional Neural Networks for Sentiment Analysis of Short Texts

Implementation of a deep convolutional neural network to analyze short texts using **Python**, B.Sc. Thesis Project.

 Secure Communication between Client and Server Implementation of a secure tunnel between a client and server for massage sharing using Java

• Radial Basis Function Neural Network

Training RBF neural networks with evolution strategy (ES) using **Python**

• Darmankade and Star Wars Websites

Implementation of a website with features and facilities similar to www.darmankade.com website and a website to collect and show the Star War movie information using PHP, HTML, CSS, JS and MySQL

• Profile Hidden Markov Model Solving triple HMM problems using Python

• Clustering, Neural Networks and Classification Implementation of Perceptron, Kmeans, Dbscan and some classification algorithms using Python

Peer to Peer File Transferring
 Implementation of a file distribution system using Java

 Image and Video Processing with OpenCV Library Processing an image and a video with OpenCV library using Python

SKILLS

• Programming Languages:

Python, Java, C

Familiar: MATLAB, VHDL, Verilog, Assembly, Shell Script

• Web Development:

 $\mathsf{HTML}, \mathsf{CSS}, \mathsf{JavaScript}, \mathsf{PHP}, \mathsf{Laravel}$

• Database Systems:

SQL, Familiar with MongoDB

· Search Engine

Implementation of some parts of a search engine Python

Search Algorithms

Implementation of graph and tree search algorithms in artificial intelligence for solving two problems using lava

• Online Store Database

Designing database of an online store using MySQL

Color Image Quantization

Implementation of quantization methods such as median cut algorithm and dithering on an image using MATLAB

• Distributed Calculator

Implementation of a calculator which performs calculations requested by a client on a server and sends results back to client using **Java**

· Chat Room

Implementation of a chat room in which people can talk in groups using **Python**

Associations

Implementation of FP-Growth and Apriori algorithms using weka library in **Phyton**

Music-Website

A website which provides services related to music such as introducing new songs or upcoming concerts to users using **Laravel**

• Data Science and AI:

Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit-Learn **Familiar:** Pytorch, Theano, sciPy, TensorFlow

• Operating Systems:

Windows, Linux

Miscellaneous:

LaTeX, Git, OpenCV, Tkinter, Microsoft Office, Py-Charm, IntelliJ IDEA, PhpStorm

Languages

- Persian (Native)
- English (Fluent) TOEFL iBT: $97/120 (25^R, 25^L, 21^S, 26^W)$

REFERENCES

• Hamid Ganji, Associate Professor

Head of Gas Research Division, Research Institute of Petroleum Industry(RIPI) Email: ganjih@ripi.ir

• Saeid Shokri, Assistant Professor

Manager of Technology and Innovation Group, Research Institute of Petroleum Industry(RIPI) Email: shokris@ripi.ir

• Hossein Zeinali, Assistant Professor

Member of Artificial Intelligent and Robotics Group, Computer Eng. Dept, Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic)

Email: hzeinali@aut.ac.ir

Mohammad Mehdi Ebadzadeh, Professor

Member of Artificial Intelligent and Robotics Group, Computer Eng. Dept, Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic)

Email: ebadzadeh@aut.ac.ir